fasttrackfundraising.com 2009-09-22

# Fundraising Company Privacy Policy – FastTrack Fundraising

[Home](http://www.fasttrackfundraising.com/) » **Fundraising Company Privacy Policy**

**SECURITY & PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
Effective November 20, 2002

**I. General Information About Our Privacy Practices**

FastTrack Fundraising Company is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our users and maintaining a secure online environment for our online fundraising programs. Our Privacy Statement covers our World Wide Web sites found at:

This Privacy Statement is effective as of the date written above and is designed to meet the following principles and practices: 

  * We fully disclose what information is collected on our sites and how we use that information; 
  * Campaign organizers, participants and supporters who participate in our online campaign programs may choose whether they want to continue to receive communications from us; 
  * We provide our registered campaign organizers with access to their account information and the ability to modify that information; and 
  * We are dedicated to creating a secure environment for user information and use an advanced network server security system to safeguard user information. 

In the more detailed description of our privacy practices below, when we use the term "you," we are referring to registered campaign organizers, participants, supporters and general users of our web sites who order campaign products or information from our web sites. When we use the term "personal information," we are referring to a user's first and last name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. 

Violating our privacy policy is cause for termination of your campaign. In addition, FastTrack Fundraising company reserves the right to cooperate with municipal, state and federal officials in any law-enforcement investigation requiring either personal information or reports about lawful or unlawful user activities on this site.

**II. FastTrack Fundraising Sections**

**Information Collected Through the Traditional Fundraising Programs**

We offer traditional campaign program products through FastTrack Fundraising. You may order free samples of products online, or request that a consultant contact you to take your campaign program order. You may also call our toll-free Order Desk to order your free samples. If you choose to submit orders or requests online, you will need to provide us with the necessary fulfillment information through our online order or request form. All personal information you submit to us through FastTrack Fundraising will only be used by us and our third-party suppliers and transactional companies for the purpose of fulfilling your order or request. FastTrack Fundraising may contact you with informational updates and communications, which you may always opt-out of as described below.

**Information Collected Through FastTrack Fundraising's Website**

**Registration Information**

In order to use our services, and/or to receive a free information kit, campaign organizers must complete an online registration form or call our toll-free number at **1.866.432.7838**. When registering online or by phone, campaign organizers need to supply contact information, relevant affiliation(s), and details related to their fundraising campaign. We collect this information from fundraising campaign organizers to assess the organizer's fundraising needs and to respond to them with information relevant to their request.

**III. Specific Information Pratices For All FastTrack Fundraising Sites**

**Order Information**

To purchase or order sample campaign products through any of our sites, you will need to provide order information (which may include credit card information). If you are purchasing campaign products from us, once your credit card has been approved by our third-party transactional company for the amount equaling the total of the supporter's desired purchases, the third-party supplier(s) will receive all relevant purchase details (item description, quantity, etc.) needed to fulfill the order. All personal information collected during the ordering process is used solely for order processing, billing and shipping.

**Information Sharing**

As detailed above, FastTrack Fundraising company does not give your personal information to third parties not associated with our campaign products or services. Our third-party suppliers use a variety of external delivery companies to ship orders, and a third-party firm processes the campaign supporters' credit cards for goods purchased. These companies, by contractual agreement with us, are not permitted to retain, store or use personally identifiable customer information except for order processing and fulfillment. 

**Log Files and Cookies**

Cookies are a small line of text generated by a site's server and sent to a user's browser, which enable the browser and server to better communicate with each other. We use cookies to analyze traffic patterns, for statistical analysis, to enhance your navigation of our web site, to tailor Web content, and to track login names, passwords and click stream data on the eFundrsaising.com site. We do not use cookies to track your navigation and usage of other web sites on the Internet. The only log information collected is non-personally identifying data, such as time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is not linked to a user account. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you can refuse to accept cookies. Refusing to accept a FastTrack Fundraising cookie may disable some enhanced navigation features that our cookies provide, but will not disable you from using the FastTrack Fundraising web site.

**Surveys & Contests**

All surveys generated by FastTrack Fundraising are distributed with detailed information concerning the reason for the survey, the nature of the information that will be collected and the manner in which the information will be used. 

**Campaign Information and Newsletters**

FastTrack Fundraising may periodically contact you by phone, mail or e-mail to inform you of campaign products and services. If you do not wish to receive further communications from us, you may opt-out by using the unsubscribe option in our e-mail correspondence, calling our toll-free number at   
**1.866.432.7838** , or by sending an e-mail to [customerservice@fasttrackfundraising.com](mailto:customerservice@fasttrackfundraising.com) requesting to be removed from the e-mail list. 

**Accessing and Updating Your Information**

For online fundraising campaigns, campaign organizers may access and modify their account information by accessing their account profiles using their user ID and password. Supporters may request any changes by calling our toll-free number at:   
**1.866.432.7838** , or by sending an e-mail to [customerservice@fasttrackfundraising.com ](mailto:customerservice@fasttrackfundraising.com)

**Security**

FastTrack Fundraising company realizes that a secure online environment is of utmost importance to protect your personal and financial information. We take strong security precautions both online and offline. 

All credit card information we collect online is encrypted using Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology, a leading advanced network server security system. We decrypt the information only at the point of processing through FastTrack Fundraising's ordering system, further ensuring the security of your information. In order to protect your data offline, FastTrack Fundraising's employee access to sensitive information is restricted, and only authorized personnel may access specific information as needed . 

**Acceptable Use**

FastTrack Fundraising is to be used only for fundraising campaigns. FastTrack Fundraising reserves the right to terminate any campaign, including all e-mail access to the campaign account, if we determine that the campaign may be illegal, unethical, misleading or in contravention of any federal, state or municipal laws, regulations or bylaws. 

**E-Mail Restrictions**

FastTrack Fundraising company is committed to responsible Internet commerce. We do not tolerate use of the FastTrack Fundraising system for non-campaign e-mails or any e-mail that includes material that FastTrack Fundraising, in its sole discretion, deems inappropriate. Sending non-fundraising or inappropriate e-mail from an FastTrack Fundraising account is cause for immediate termination of access to that account. 

**Links to Other Sites**

FastTrack Fundraising contains links to other sites on the Internet. Although FastTrack Fundraising company is diligent about the selection of its partners and affiliates, we are neither responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites or any other sites you may visit on the Internet. For your own information and security, we recommend that you carefully read a site's individual privacy policies prior to using that site. 

**Changes to the FastTrack Fundraising Privacy Statement**

We are dedicated to fair information practices and do not anticipate any changes in our privacy practices that would substantially change how we describe our practices to you. However, due to rapidly changing technology, and to ensure that we can provide the best service to our customers, FastTrack Fundraising reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement. We will always give you notice of such changes by prominently posting such changes on our website before they take effect. Nothing contained in this Statement is intended to create a contract or agreement between FastTrack Fundraising company and any user visiting the site or providing identifying information in any form.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact [info@fasttrackfundraising.com](mailto:info@fasttrackfundraising.com). 

Please forward any additional questions or concerns to [info@fasttrackfundraising.com](mailto:info@fasttrackfundraising.com) We will use our best efforts to respond to inquiries by return e-mail within 72 hours.
